Finding Aid for George Romney Papers 1920s-1973
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Sound Recordings
  - Chronological Series I, 7 inch reel-to-reel audiotapes
    - 1966
      - George Romney interview, Lou Gordon Show, 1966 October 16, Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 3 3/4 ips
        - [Part 1], [852178-SR-404-1]; mp3 file; (George Romney interviewed on the Lou Gordon show, discussing his opinions on the Civil Rights Movement and his skepticism on the war in Vietnam and other topics.)
        - [Part 2], [852178-SR-404-2]; mp3 file; (George Romney interviewed on the Lou Gordon show, discussing his opinions on the Civil Rights Movement and his skepticism on the war in Vietnam and other topics.)
      - GR speech, Jackson Telethon October 18, 1966, 7-1/2 ips (Box 370)
      - GR speech, 15th Annual Boys Day Civic dinner, Boys Club, Detroit October 19, 1966, 7-1/2 ips (Box 370)
      - GR speech, Romney Telethon "Ask the Action team," Kalamazoo, Michigan October 25, 1966, 7-1/2 ips (Box 370)
      - GR speech, "Ask the Action team," Grand Rapids, Michigan November 3, 1966, 2 tapes 3-3/4 ips (Box 370)
    - 1967
      - GR speech, Lincoln Day Banquet - Oakland County, Michigan February 15, 1967, 3-3/4 ips (Box 370)
      - GR speech, Anchorage, Alaska February 18, 1967, 7-1/2 ips (Box 370)
      - GR airport speech, Romney and Hickel (Governor of Alaska), and Press Conference, Captain Cook Hotel February 18, 1967, 7-1/2 ips (Box 370)
      - GR speech to precinct workers, Anchorage, Alaska February 18, 1967, 2 tapes 7-1/2 ips (Box 371)
      - GR speech, Luncheon, Salt Lake City, Utah February 20, 1967, 3-3/4 ips (Box 371)
      - GR press conference, Salt Lake City, Utah February 20, 1967, 3-3/4 ips (Box 371)
      - GR speeches 7:00 p.m. and 9:00 p.m., Salt Lake City, Utah February 20, 1967, 2 tapes 7-1/2 ips (Box 371)
      - GR speech and related, Ricks College, Rexburg, Idaho February 21, 1967, 3 tapes 7-1/2 ips (Box 371)
      - GR speech, Pocatello, Idaho February 21, 1967, 3-3/4 ips (Box 371)
      - GR speech, Albuquerque, New Mexico February 22, 1967, 7-1/2 ips (Box 371)
      - GR speech, Lincoln Day Banquet. Evansville, Indiana March 7, 1967, 3-3/4 ips (Box 371)
      - GR interview, Bob Kennedy "Contact," WBZ-TV, Boston, Massachusetts April 28, 1967, 3-3/4 ips (Box 371)
      - GR press conference May 5, 1967, 7-1/2 ips (Box 371)
      - GR press conference May 9, 1967, 7-1/2 ips (Box 371)
      - GR speech, Amway Convention May 27, 1967, 2 tapes 7-1/2 ips (Box 371)
      - GR speech, Family Life Conference, Lansing June 20, 1967, 3-3/4 ips (Box 371)
      - GR speech June 21, 1967, 7-1/2 ips (Box 371)
      - GR conference, Newark, New Jersey June 22, 1967, 7-1/2 ips (Box 371)
      - GR speeches, Monmouth Hotel, Spring Lake, New Jersey June 22, 1967, 2 tapes 7-1/2 ips (Box 371)
      - GR conference, Tax Reform, Governor's office, State Capitol, Lansing, Michigan June 22-28, 1967, 5 tapes 1-7/8 ips (Box 371)
      - George Romney press conference, Police Headquarters, Detroit, Michigan, 1967 July 23-24, Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch
        - [Part 1], [852178-SR-442-1]; mp3 file; (George Romney on a press conference declaring the state of emergency proclamation in Detroit. Tape cuts off to July 24 at 3 AM during a press conference right after the deployment of the National Guard and the situation in Detroit that evening.)
      - GR speech, National Association of County Officials, Detroit July 31, 1967, 7-1/2 ips (Box 371)
      - GR speech, Chautauqua, New York August 4, 1967, 7-1/2 ips (Box 371)
      - George Romney conference, Detroit Riot, 1967 August 22, Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7 1/2 ips
        - [Part 1], [852178-SR-445-1]; mp3 file; (Speech calling for action in managing the social issues in Detroit, including racism, employment, and housing. Remainder of the tape is Romney giving several press conferences on the subject of the Detroit Riot including the deployment of Federal troops.)
      - GR press conference, Midwest Governors, Lake of the Ozarks, Missouri August 30, 1967, 2 tapes 7-1/2 ips (Box 371)
      - GR Medicaid conference September 22, 1967, 7-1/2 ips (Box 371)
      - George Romney press conference, San Francisco, California, 1967 September 22, Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7 1/2 ips
        - [Part 1], [852178-SR-449-1]; mp3 file; (George Romney discussing government expenditures on health care and other issues using his experience as a business leader.)
      - New Detroit, 1967 October 02, Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch
        - [Part 1], [852178-SR-450-1-1]; mp3 file; (Romney's appearance before the New Detroit Committee. Introduced by Joel Hudson. Romney discusses poverty and various urban issues.)
        - [Part 1], [852178-SR-450-1-2]; mp3 file; (Romney's appearance before the New Detroit Committee. Introduced by Joel Hudson. Romney discusses poverty and various urban issues, including education.)
        - [Part 2], [852178-SR-450-2]; mp3 file; (Romney meeting with Detroit Community leaders discussing housing and other urban issues in the aftermath of the Detroit Riot.)
      - GR interview, John Chancellor - NBC October 13, 1967, 1-7/8 ips (Box 371)
      - GR speech, Bismark, South Dakota October 25, 1967, 2 tapes 3-3/4 ips and 7-1/2 ips (Box 371)
      - GR speech, Fund Raising lunch, Fargo, North Dakota October 25, 1967, 3-3/4 ips (Box 371)
      - GR speech, Mesa, Arizona October 26, 1967, 7-1/2 ips (Box 371)
      - GR speech, Phoenix, Arizona October 26, 1967, 3-3/4 ips (Box 371)
      - GR speech, Phoenix, Arizona October 26, 1967, 1-7/8 ips (Box 371)
      - GR conference. Western Republican Conference Panel: "Government with Labor and Business," October 27, 1967, 3-3/4 ips (Box 371)
      - GR speech, Field House, University of New Hampshire, Durham, New Hampshire October 30, 1967 (Box 371)
      - GR conference, University of New Hampshire October 30, 1967, 7-1/2 ips (Box 371)
      - GR speech, Senior Symposia, Dartmouth College, Hanover, New Hampshire October 30, 1967, 3 tapes 7-1/2 ips (Box 371)
      - GR speech, Vietnam War - Johnson Administration, Providence, Rhode Island October 31, 1967, 7-1/2 ips (Box 371)
      - GR speech on crime, Providence, Rhode Island October 31, 1967, 2 tapes 7-1/2 ips (Box 371)
      - GR conference, Minneapolis, Minnesota November 6, 1967, 3-3/4 ips (Box 371)
      - GR speech, Landon Lecture Series, Kansas State University, Manhattan, Kansas December 6, 1967, 7-1/2 ips (Box 371)
    - 1968
      - GR press conference, Budget briefing January 24, 1968, 1-7/8 ips (Box 371)
      - GR speech, City Club of Portland, Oregon February 23, 1968, 7-1/2 ips (Box 371)
      - GR speech, withdrawing statement. Washington Hilton, Washington, D.C. February 28, 1968, 3-3/4 ips (Box 371)
      - GR press conference, Washington Hilton March 4, 1968, 3-3/4 ips (Box 371)
      - GR address to Birmingham-Bloomfield Council on Human Relations March 21, 1968 (Box 371)
      - GR interview, The Don Sims Show, Windsor, Ontario April 16, 1968, 3-3/4 ips (Box 371)
      - GR news conference, Storm Damage to Detroit Suburbs August 18, 1968, 7-1/2 ips (Box 371)
      - GR speech, Nationalities Reception, GOP National Convention August 1968, 2 tapes 7-1/2 ips (Box 371)
      - GR and Richard Nixon discussion of self-help, private enterprise and voluntary urban programs October 1, 1968, 2 tapes (Box 371)
      - GR interview, "Contact!" Television Bob Kennedy, 1968, 3-3/4 ips (Box 371)
    - Undated
      - GR speech on Vietnam, University of Detroit, undated, 7-1/2 ips 3 tapes (Box 371)
        (tape 1 is missing)
      - GR debate, with Ferency, undated, 2 tapes 7-1/2 ips (Box 371)
      - GR speech, Michigan Week, undated, 7-1/2 ips (Box 371)
      - GR speech, Escanaba, Michigan, undated, 7-1/2 ips (Box 371)
      - GR speech, undated, 3-3/4 ips (Box 371)
      - GR conference, undated, 3-3/4 ips (Box 371)
      - GR press conference, Womens Committee for Romney, undated, 7-1/2 ips (Box 371)
      - GR press conference, Civil Rights, undated, 3-3/4 ips (Box 373)
      - GR speech, prayer breakfast, undated, 7-1/2 ips (Box 373)
      - GR press conferences, Tax Reform, Education, undated, 3-3/4 ips (Box 373)
      - GR press conference, undated, 3-3/4 ips (Box 373)
      - GR press conference, undated, 3-3/4 ips (Box 373)
      - Lou Gordon and Guy Nunn Radio interviews, 1962, Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 3 3/4 ips
        - [Part 1], [852178-SR-496-1]; mp3 file; (Tape 1; Lou Gordon interviewing Lenore Romney. Announcers introduction states content is on fiscal reform and austerity. Content is difficult to hear.)
      - Lou Gordon and Guy Nunn Radio interviews, 1962, Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 3 3/4 ips
        - [Part 1], [852178-SR-497-1]; mp3 file; (Tape 2; Multiple recordings mixed into a single tape. First part of tape is a excerpt from a Lou Gordon interview, mentioning politics and Frank Beadle. Interview with George Romney discussing the relationship between the governor's office and the state legislature. Excerpts from the program "Telescope" interviewing Governor John Swainson. )
      - Lou Gordon and Guy Nunn Radio interviews, 1962, Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 3 3/4 ips
        - [Part 1], [852178-SR-498-1]; mp3 file; (Tape 3; Discussing Governor Swainson's appointee for the position of Insurance Commissioner. Political campaign for George Romney during his 1962 campaign.)
      - Lou Gordon and Guy Nunn Radio interviews, [Undated], Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 1-7/8 ips
        - [Part 1], [852178-SR-499-1]; mp3 file; (Tape 4; George Romney interviews during his 1962 campaign. References to both John Swainson and George Romney on the Lou Gordon and Guy Nunn radio programs.)
      - Lou Gordon and Guy Nunn Radio interviews, 1962, Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 1-7/8 ips
        - [Part 1], [852178-SR-500-1]; mp3 file; (Tape 5; 41:20 appears the start of content. Includes news reports on Christmas Island Nuclear Tests, a radio program, and other content that is hard to discern. Tape has note indicating overmixing of material.)
      - Lou Gordon and Guy Nunn Radio interviews, 1962, Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7 1/2 ips
        - [Part 1], [852178-SR-501-1]; mp3 file; (Tape 6; Excerpt from the "Telescope" UAW Television program, critiquing Romney's campaign and his relationship with organized labor.)
      - Lou Gordon and Guy Nunn Radio interviews, [Undated], Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7 1/2 ips
        - [Part 1], [852178-SR-502-1]; mp3 file; (Tape 7; Mike & Louie oratory on Stock Market. A humorous discussion between two speakers Stock Market speculation and the Kennedy Administration.)
        - [Part 2], [852178-SR-502-2]; mp3 file; (Tape 7; Miscellanous recordings of children singing and radio programs. )
      - Lou Gordon and Guy Nunn Radio interviews, 1962, Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7 1/2 ips
        - [Part 1], [852178-SR-503-1]; mp3 file; (Tape 8; Guy Nunn critiquing George Romney during the 1962 Michigan Governor Campaign.)
      - Lou Gordon and Guy Nunn Radio interviews, [Undated], Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7 1/2 ips
        - [Part 1], [852178-SR-504-1]; mp3 file; (Tape 9; UAW "Telescope" program, George Romney on the program. )
      - Lou Gordon and Guy Nunn Radio interviews, [Undated], Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7 1/2 ips
        - [Part 1], [852178-SR-505-1]; mp3 file; (Tape 10; Humorous performance of a phone call between character "Charlie" and George Romney.)
  - Press Conference Series
    (individual tapes often cover multiple press conference dates)
    - April 4, 1963-December 18, 1963 nos. 1-20 (Box 373)
    - January 8, 1964-April 9, 1966 nos. 21-54 (Box 374)
    - April 11, 1966-January 15, 1969 nos. 55-89 (Box 375)
  - Chronological Series II, 5-inch tapes
    - 1955
      - GR interview, Jack White, "Designs for You," December 10, 1955, 7-1/2 ips (Box 21-E)
    - 1956
      - George Romney speech; Rambler Announcement, 1956, Audio Reel-to-Reel, 5 inch, 3 3/4 ips
        - [Part 1], [852178-SR-596-1]; mp3 file; (Announcement of the American Motors Corporation Rambler car with George Romney discussing the merits of the car to dealers during conference. Hum and buzz throughout recording. )
    - 1959
      - GR speech, Rotary Club, Statler Hilton, Detroit March 4, 1959, 7-1/2 ips (Box 21-E)
      - GR speech, National Conference of Christians and Jews, Los Angeles May 20, 1959, 3-3/4 ips (Box 21-E)
      - GR speech, Citizens of Michigan organizational meeting, Lansing, Michigan September 21, 1959, 3-3/4 ips (Box 21-E)
    - 1960
      - GR speech, "Listener's Digest," Glendale, California July 1960, 7-1/2 ips (Box 21-E)
    - 1961
      - GR interview, Mike Stanley WCAU, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania September 16, 1961, 7-1/2 ips (Box 21-E)
    - 1962 (Box 376)
      - GR interview, Radio WCCO, Minneapolis, Minnesota May 2, 1962, 2 tapes 7-1/2 ips (Box 376)
      - GR speech, Houghton, Michigan May 12, 1962, 1-7/8 ips (Box 376)
      - GR speech, GOP Rally, Owosso June 7, 1962, 3-3/4 ips (Box 376)
      - GR interview, Apportionment, TV talk July 21, 1962, 7-1/2 ips (Box 376)
      - George Romney Campaign Spot, Lou Gordon Show, 1962 August 23, Audio Reel-to-Reel, 5 inch, 7 1/2 ips
        - [Part 1], [852178-SR-607-1]; mp3 file; (Brief campaign advertisement by George Romney on the Lou Gordon Show.)
      - GR speech re: education October 12, 1962, 2 tapes 3-3/4 ips (Box 376)
      - GR Radio Spots October 23, 1962, 7-1/2 ips (Box 376)
      - GR press conference October 25, 1962, 7-1/2 ips (Box 376)
    - 1963
      - GR speech, Grand Hotel, Mackinac Island June 16, 1963, 3-3/4 ips (Box 376)
      - GR conference, Tax Reform program, Grand Rapids, Michigan June 20, 1963, 3-3/4 ips (Box 376)
      - GR interview, WJBK September 7, 1963, 7-1/2 ips (Box 376)
    - 1964
      - GR theme song of 1964 Campaign 1964, 5 tapes 7-1/2 ips (nos. 1-4); 3-3/4 ips (no.5) (Box 376)
    - 1965
      - GR interview, Ann Arbor, Michigan March 4, 1965, 1-7/8 ips (Box 376)
      - GR press conference, Tax Reform March 27, 1965, 1-7/8 ips (Box 376)
      - GR speech, Holland, Michigan April 10, 1965, 3-3/4 ips (Box 376)
      - GR press conferences September 11, 1965, 1-7/8 ips (Box 376)
    - 1966
      - GR speech, Woodhaven Stamping Plant Dedication, Ford Motor Company April 15, 1966, 7-1/2 ips (Box 376)
      - GR speech, Bethany College, West Virginia June 4, 1966, 1-7/8 ips (Box 376)
      - GR press conference, Cincinnati June 21, 1966, 3-3/4 ips (Box 376)
      - GR speech, Perry-Davis Hotel, Petoskey, Michigan August 20, 1966, 7-1/2 ips (Box 376)
      - George Romney and Zolton Ferency Debate, AFL-CIO Convention, Detroit, 1966 September 27, Audio Reel-to-Reel, 5 inch, 3 3/4 ips
        - [Part 1], [852178-SR-628-1]; mp3 file; (Debate between George Romney and Zolton Ferency during the 1966 Michigan Gubernatorial election.)
        - [Part 2], [852178-SR-628-2]; mp3 file; (Debate between George Romney and Zolton Ferency during the 1966 Michigan Gubernatorial election.)
      - Debate between George Romney and Zolton Economic Club of Detroit, Cobo Hall, Detroit, 1966 October 03, Audio Reel-to-Reel, 5 inch, 1-7/8 ips
        - [Part 1], [852178-SR-629-1]; mp3 file; (Debate between George Romney and Zolton Ferency during the 1966 Michigan Gubernatorial election.)
      - George Romney speech to Baptist Ministers Conference, 1966 October 18, Audio Reel-to-Reel, 5 inch, 3 3/4 ips
        - [Part 1], [852178-SR-630-1]; mp3 file; (George Romney discussing economic difficulties, racial discrimination, and housing.)
      - GR speech, Fund raising dinner for Expo Building October 31, 1966, 3-3/4 ips (Box 376)
      - GR speech, Christmas message December 1966, 7-1/2 ips (Box 376)
    - 1967
      - GR message, Tax Reform message to the Legislature February 2, 1967, 1-7/8 ips (Box 376)
      - GR conference, Romney Telethon February 6, 1967, 1-7/8 ips (Box 376)
      - GR speech, Salt Lake City, Utah February 20, 1967, 3-3/4 ips (Box 376)
      - GR address to Utah Legislature February 20, 1967, 3-3/4 ips (Box 376)
      - GR press conference and speech, American Iron and Steel Institute May 1967, 1-7/8 ips (Box 376)
      - GR press conference, Civic Center, Lansing, Michigan May 1967, 1-7/8 ips (Box 376)
      - GR speech and press conferences, Wisconsin June 6, 1967, 1-7/8 ips (Box 376)
      - GR message to Legislature, Civil Rights June 9, 1967, 7-1/2 ips (Box 376)
      - GR interview, Face Michigan, WKZO Kalamazoo June 13, 1967 (Box 376)
      - George Romney conference, Detroit Riot, 1967 July 24-25, Audio Reel-to-Reel, 5 inch, 7 1/2 ips
        - [Part 1], [852178-SR-642-1]; mp3 file; (George Romney declaring a Public State of Emergency in Detroit during the 12th Street Riots and incidents of sniping in the area.)
      - Urban Tour press conferences, meetings, etc., 1967 September 11-29, Audio Reel-to-Reel, 5 inch
        - [Part 1], [852178-SR-643-1]; mp3 file; (Tape 1; Bill Walsh, director of Urban Dynamics Program, discussing his program for Governor Romney. Romney then describing damage in the 12th Street Riot.)
        - [Part 2], [852178-SR-643-2]; mp3 file; (Tape 1; Irma Kraft, business education teacher with George Romney during his Urban Tour on the subject of education and employment prospects in Detroit.)
      - Urban Tour press conferences, meetings, etc., 1967 September 11-29, Audio Reel-to-Reel, 5 inch
        - [Part 1], [852178-SR-644-1]; mp3 file; (Tape 2; Romney on his urban tour discussing urban problems, racism, and poverty.)
        - [Part 2], [852178-SR-644-2]; mp3 file; (Tape 2; Romney at Gracie Mansion, New York City, after a prior meeting with Mayor Lindsay of New York. Includes some possible mentions of Romney's political futures.)
      - Urban Tour press conferences, meetings, etc., 1967 September 11-29, Audio Reel-to-Reel, 5 inch
        - [Part 1], [852178-SR-645-1]; mp3 file; (Tape 3; Dictation (not Romney) of text on urban housing in the Brooklyn area from Romney's urban tour.)
        - [Part 2], [852178-SR-645-2]; mp3 file; (Tape 3; from George Romney's urban tour. Begins with dictation on George Romney's meeting with leaders in Rochester, New York.)
      - Urban Tour press conferences, meetings, etc., 1967 September 11-29, Audio Reel-to-Reel, 5 inch
        - [Part 1], [852178-SR-646-1]; mp3 file; (Tape 4; Dictation of conclusion of the sixth Stop of Romney's tour of New York with Don Elliott.)
        - [Part 2], [852178-SR-646-2]; mp3 file; (Tape 4; Romney press conference in Indianapolis on his experiences with the different cities he visited during his Urban Tour. Includes further dictation of meetings from Romney's tour.)
      - Urban Tour press conferences, meetings, etc., 1967 September 11-29, Audio Reel-to-Reel, 5 inch
        - [Part 1], [852178-SR-647-1]; mp3 file; (Tape 5; Romney speaking in St. Louis during his urban tour. Discussing challenges facing urban areas.)
        - [Part 2], [852178-SR-647-2]; mp3 file; (Tape 5; Romney speaking in St. Louis during his urban tour. Discussing challenges facing urban areas.)
      - Urban Tour press conferences, meetings, etc., 1967 September 11-29, Audio Reel-to-Reel, 5 inch
        - [Part 1], [852178-SR-648-1]; mp3 file; (Tape 6; Highlights from Romney's tour in St. Louis. Dictation of meetings and speeches from Romney. Some issues with consistent tape speed on this tape.)
      - Urban Tour press conferences, meetings, etc., 1967 September 11-29, Audio Reel-to-Reel, 5 inch
        - [Part 1], [852178-SR-649-1]; mp3 file; (Tape 7; Some variations in the speed of recording. Romney and unknown speaker discussing poverty and other urban issues.)
        - [Part 2], [852178-SR-649-2]; mp3 file; (Tape 7; Romney and unknown speaker discussing poverty and other urban issues.)
      - Urban Tour press conferences, meetings, etc., 1967 September 11-29, Audio Reel-to-Reel, 5 inch
        - [Part 1], [852178-SR-650-1-1]; mp3 file; (Tape 8; During Romney's visit to Minnesota. Discussing the develop of the planned community of Jonathan, Minnesota. Discussion turns to the subject of food and nutrition from General Mills corporation. Also includes portions of St. Louis, Indianapolis, and Salt Lake City visits.)
        - [Part 1], [852178-SR-650-1-2]; mp3 file; (Tape 8; 6 Minute clip with George Romney speaking. Romney discussing his remarks on his trip to Vietnam and his perspectives of the conflict.)
        - [Part 2], [852178-SR-650-2]; mp3 file; (Tape 8; Continuation on the notes of the Women's Anti-Crime Crusade. Dictations from Romney's Indianapolis trip.)
      - Urban Tour press conferences, meetings, etc., 1967 September 11-29, Audio Reel-to-Reel, 5 inch
        - [Part 1], [852178-SR-651-1]; mp3 file; (Tape 9; Silence between 17:10 and 22:20. Press Conference with Romney, answering questions about his works on poverty, his campaign announcement, and urban development.)
      - Urban Tour press conferences, meetings, etc., 1967 September 11-29, Audio Reel-to-Reel, 5 inch
        - [Part 1], [852178-SR-652-1]; mp3 file; (Tape 10; Romney's meeting with Bay Area Mexican Americans Community Conference.)
        - [Part 2], [852178-SR-652-2-1]; mp3 file; (Tape 10; Romney in San Francisco discussing the relationship between Mexican Americans and other minority communities in California.)
        - [Part 2], [852178-SR-652-2-2]; mp3 file; (Tape 10; George Romney in San Francisco. Content is difficult to hear. )
        - [Part 2], [852178-SR-652-2-2]; mp3 file; (Tape 10; George Romney in San Francisco. Content is difficult to hear. )
        - [Part 2], [852178-SR-652-2-3]; mp3 file; (Tape 10; Romney's telephone message to Republican Leader Conference in Mackinac Island from Los Angeles, California.)
        - [Part 2], [852178-SR-652-2-3]; mp3 file; (Tape 10; Romney's telephone message to Republican Leader Conference in Mackinac Island from Los Angeles, California.)
      - Urban Tour press conferences, meetings, etc., 1967 September 11-29, Audio Reel-to-Reel, 5 inch
        - [Part 1], [852178-SR-653-1]; mp3 file; (Tape 11; Meeting with Romney and other urban leaders discussing Emmitt Grogan, "Legendary Founder of the Hippie Movement.")
        - [Part 2], [852178-SR-653-2]; mp3 file; (Tape 11; Romney in San Francisco, California. Actualities during Romney's visit to Glide Methodist Church during Romney's urban tour.)
      - Urban Tour press conferences, meetings, etc., 1967 September 11-29, Audio Reel-to-Reel, 5 inch
        - [Part 1], [852178-SR-654-1]; mp3 file; (Tape 12; Conversation between Romney and unidentified Black Muslim discussing struggles of urban environments and the debate around the use of violence for social change.)
        - [Part 2], [852178-SR-654-2]; mp3 file; (Tape 12; Community School Briefing, Atlanta, Georgia. Subjects discussed are education and school quality in Atlanta.)
      - Urban Tour press conferences, meetings, etc., 1967 September 11-29, Audio Reel-to-Reel, 5 inch
        - [Part 1], [852178-SR-655-1]; mp3 file; (Tape 13; Romney in Atlanta as part of his 1967 Urban Tour. Press Conference in Marriott Hotel.)
        - [Part 2], [852178-SR-655-2]; mp3 file; (Tape 13; Romney in Atlanta as part of his 1967 Urban Tour. Press Conference in Marriott Hotel.)
      - Urban Tour press conferences, meetings, etc., 1967 September 11-29, Audio Reel-to-Reel, 5 inch
        - [Part 1], [852178-SR-656-1]; mp3 file; (Tape 14; Romney in Atlanta, includes portions of content from a church service Atlanta.)
        - [Part 2], [852178-SR-656-2]; mp3 file; (Tape 14; Panel Discussion at Peachtree Courthouse, Atlanta. Discussing government structure and education issues in Atlanta.)
      - Urban Tour press conferences, meetings, etc., 1967 September 11-29, Audio Reel-to-Reel, 5 inch